http://merchantservicesconsulting.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for merchantservicesconsulting.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 888.522.6537 or via email.
Videos: Did you know?
Fraud, PCI Compliance, Terminals, Interchange and Charge Backs
Contact MSCG
A friendly, knowledgeable Professional Payment Industry representative is ready to help you.
Credit Card • Debit Card • Gift Card • Check Acceptance
Call: 888.5.BANKER
Online: Express Info Form
We offer a Complimentary Quote. No OBLIGATION.
• New to Merchant Processing?  • Existing Merchant Account?
• Upgrading to New Techonology?  • Going Mobile?
Find out how Merchant Services Consulting can help you increase your bottom line today.
Do you want updates in your inbox?
Don't miss important changes and updates. Merchant Services Consulting stays current so you don't miss out.
Merchant Services Consulting Group, Inc.
Copyright © 2020 All Rights Reserved
